<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="waypoint_todo">You didn\'t find this waypoint yet!</string>
    <string name="waypoint_reached_title">Waypoint found</string>
    <string name="waypoint_reached">You have arrived at your waypoint. Next waypoint:</string>
    <string name="waypoint_name_activity">Waypoint</string>
    <string name="waypoint_check">I did visit this waypoint</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>
    <string name="RouteSelectorText">Choose route:</string>
    <string name="route_offroute_title">You\'re going off route</string>
    <string name="route_offroute">Go back to route</string>
    <string name="route_finished_title">Route completed</string>
    <string name="route_finished">You have completed the route.</string>
    <string name="Route">Historical KM</string>
    <string name="popup_question">Are you sure you want to reset your progress?</string>
    <string name="information_name_activity">Information</string>
    <string name="information_about_title">"Application explination "</string>
    <string name="decline">NO</string>
    <string name="agree">YES</string>
    <string name="information_about_app">"In this application you can find a map with a route. This application will help you follow the route by your choice. The route follows different waypoints. At each waypoint you get extra information about the waypoint. Good luck and have fun!  "</string>

    //Descriptions
    <string name="description_1">Diagonally across the street on the Grote Markt is the city hall of Breda
and also the branch office of the VVV.

The main entrance of the stand house is above the landing, which is guarded
is made by two sandstone lions. The town hall, as it looks now,
only came about in 1767. They are actually four houses, which then through the
master builder of Orange, Philips Willem Schonck, behind one façade
hidden. The oldest part is the large hall. Already in the fifteenth century
in addition, a so-called \ "Cleyn raedthuys \" was put into use. It came in 1898
the right-most house, the \ 'Lying Deer \' there, that is still a separate one
facade. has.

Despite the fact that the town hall has only limited opening hours for the
public, we want to give you the following information about its inside anyway
do not remember.
Lady Justice above the main entrance and the wooden statue in the back of the hall
indicate that justice was also used in the town hall in the past.
The counter of the former court, once standing against the back wall of the
hall, is now kept in the Breda \ 's Museum.
On the left is a large copy of the famous Velasques \ 'Las painting
Lanzas ", that the surrender of Breda to the Spanish commander Spinola (1625)
portrays.
The original painting is in the Prado in Madrid.
The town hall is still used for public council meetings and for it
marriages. The mayor, aldermen and municipal officials
houses since February 1992 in the new Stadskantoor on the Claudius
Prinsenlaan in Breda. We walk through the gatehouse to the right of the town hall
on the Stadserf. In the middle of this square the figurine reminds De
Peat skipper by Gerarda Rueb, to the legendary robbery in 1590 of
Adriaan van Bergen with his Peat ship. (The Breda Tourist Office is selling one of these
replica).</string>
    <string name="description_2">You walk back through the gate to the Grote Markt and turn left.
The second street on the left is St. Janstraat. You enter here.

At the corner of Halstraat / St. Janstraat we are in front of the building with the
pillars: the garrison command. In the past the building \ "hoofdwacht \"
called. Before that head guard moved in, the St. stood at this place
Janskapel with again behind the buildings of the Knights Order of St. Jan.
The members of this order cared for the sick and poor here.
The street name is reminiscent of these Knights of St. Jan. in the chapel the
major city fire of 1534.

The St. Janstraat once was also called the Veterstraat, probably after
the huydvetters or tanners, who work in the St. Janstraat
exercised.
On your right in St. Janstraat is the Antonius van Padua church, a
striking richly executed water management church. This church was built in 1836 as
first catholic church after the shroud period, which was officially built
might be. In 1853 it became the first bishop's church (cathedral) of the
new diocese in Breda. The seat of the bishop of Breda returned after one
absence of 32 years at the beginning of 2001 back to the Antonius Church
who thereby regained the status of cathedral. Be at the front
clearly see the three types of antique columns. From the bottom to the top:
Doric, Ionic and Corinthian columns. The image above the entrance sets
\ "the Religion \" for. The beautiful wooden pulpit is immediately inside
on. It depicts the life of St. Anthony in various panels.
A little further there are remnants or just memories of two
very important court houses, the Huis Ocrum, which until 1994 contained the Art Academy
St. Joost was established and the Hersbeeck House, now a rectory. In 1667
the English envoys who participated in the
Peace negotiations from Breda. The representatives of the Council of State
used the building (No. 16) when they were on a business trip in the city,
but King Louis Napoleon also stayed there. The bay window of this building
had a controlling function: the pastor could keep a close eye on who is
went to church.
From 1848 to 1952, the Ocrum House (no. 18) was a Roman orphanage. You can
you can still see from the cobblestones that are on the 19th century facade of it
academy building. The red color of this house (after the
restoration applied) will become a beautiful gray red over the years
color of this house (applied after the restoration) will pass through the course of
get a nice gray red color for years.
</string>
    <string name="description_3">At the end of St. Jansstraat you turn right into Molenstraat.

In the Molenstraat you can see the Library, designed by architect
Herman Hertzberger. Because the Molenstraat is quite narrow, the architect has
space created by giving the library sloping walls. On the
location of the library (on the corner with the Old Vest) used to be
a gate. Above this gate was \'s Heeren Gevangenhuys, where the
the most severely punished. The place is still with pebbles in it
asphalt indicated; the asphalt road is the site of the old city canal.</string>
    <string name="description_4">In addition to the Kloosterkazerne, the Chassé Theater was built, also designed by Herman Hertzberger, the designer of the library.
The front end of the adjacent barracks building enters this new theater. The Casino and the Chassé Theater have a joint entrance.</string>
    <string name="description_5">On the corner of Vlaszak and Veemarktstraat you can see an indication of the former Gasthuispoort in the sidewalk.
A number of stones have also been preserved.</string>
    <string name="description_6">This is the Willem MarkxTuin.</string>
    <string name="description_7">This is the VVV.</string>
    <string name="description_8">When you cross the bridge, you will see it on your left
Nassau-Baroni monument.

At the entrance to the city park, it
Valkenberg is a monument
that you tell something about the
history of the city of Breda, but
especially about the Lords of the city from it
House of Nassau and the 500-year-old band
between Breda and the House of Nassau.
On July 3, 1905, the Nassau-Baronie
monument, as it is officially called, with
much festive display by Queen
Wilhelmina revealed. The image remembers
to the fact that in 1404 Count Engelbert,
the first Breda Nassau and his wife, Johanna van Polanen,
were inaugurated as Lord and Lady of Breda.
The designer is the well-known Dr. P.J.H. Cuypers, which among other things
Rijksmuseum and Central Station in Amsterdam.
On this monument are not only the coats of arms of twenty
municipalities in and around the Baronie but also the
Lion of Nassau towering above everything with a royal crown,
sword and coat of arms. In the three reliefs, the "happy incomplete" is
of Count Engelbert and his wife. The Poorters
offer the key to the city.</string>
    <string name="description_9">This is the Light House.</string>
    <string name="description_10">THis is the Stadhouderspoort.</string>
    <string name="description_12">This is the Grote Kerk.</string>
    <string name="description_13">This is the Bevrijdingsmonument.</string>
    <string name="description_11">At the Vishal you enter the Vismarktstraat; this street ends at the Havermarkt.  From the place where the fish market (1725) still indicates that there was a lively trade in sea fish here in the past, we walk through the Vismarktstraat to the Havermarkt. This market has been the entertainment center of Breda from the 1960s to the present day. Despite the name Havermarkt, it must be stated that the cereals are not here; but were traded on the Grote Markt. However, vegetables, eggs and butter were supplied and sold by farmers from the area. A leather market was also held here in the seventeenth century. The old names of this square were Groenmarkt, Botermarkt and Korenmarkt, which indicates the earlier functions a little better.  This was laid out around 1490 as a widening of the Visserstraat. If you grab a beer on a terrace on this delightful square in the summer, you will soon discover (even without that beer) that this square offers the best view of the large tower of the Grote Kerk. From this place you can also admire the beautiful broad substructure of that tower. There is much to see on this square. To the left on the corner of Havermarkt and Reigerstraat you will see the house \'De Arent\', built around 1490. It now has a seventeenth-century stepped gable and was completely restored in 1966 and converted into a restaurant. Opposite you on the Havermarkt are two more buildings that deserve your attention. Havermarkt number 5 dates from the sixteenth and seventeenth centuries. \'De Vogelstruys\' on Havermarkt 21 is a remarkable seventeenth-century monument with a high, non-symmetrical stepped gable. This house has also had many functions and destinations over the centuries. It was, among other things, a refuge house for the sisters of Catharinadal in the seventeenth century. Four statuettes were made for the \'De Troubadour\' statue, which adorns the end of Havermarkt. The other three were unveiled in Diest, Orange and Dillenburg, the sister cities of Breda in the Union of Orange Cities, which was established in 1963. A little further in the Visserstraat (no. 31), on the right-hand side, is a beautiful brick house from the 17th century with the remains of a sixteenth-century gothic house, called the Three Moors.</string>
    <string name="gps_disabled">The application is unable to use GPS at this moment</string>
    <string name="gps_enabled">The application is able to use GPS</string>
    <string name="gps_off">GPS is off</string>
    <string name="gps_on">GPS is on</string>

</resources>