<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="waypoint_todo">You didn\'t find this waypoint yet!</string>
    <string name="waypoint_reached_title">Waypoint found</string>
    <string name="waypoint_reached">You have arrived at your waypoint. Next waypoint:</string>
    <string name="waypoint_name_activity">Waypoint</string>
    <string name="waypoint_check">I did visit this waypoint</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>
    <string name="RouteSelectorText">Choose route:</string>
    <string name="route_offroute_title">You\'re going off route</string>
    <string name="route_offroute">Go back to route</string>
    <string name="route_finished_title">Route completed</string>
    <string name="route_finished">You have completed the route.</string>
    <string name="Route">Historical KM</string>
    <string name="popup_question">Are you sure you want to reset your progress?</string>
    <string name="information_name_activity">Information</string>
    <string name="information_about_title">"Application explination "</string>
    <string name="decline">NO</string>
    <string name="agree">YES</string>
    <string name="information_about_app">"In this application you can find a map with a route. This application will help you follow the route by your choice. The route follows different waypoints. At each waypoint you get extra information about the waypoint. Good luck and have fun!  "</string>

    //Descriptions
    <string name="description_1"></string>
    <string name="description_2"></string>
    <string name="description_3"></string>
    <string name="description_4"></string>
    <string name="description_5"></string>
    <string name="description_6"></string>
    <string name="description_7"></string>
    <string name="description_8"></string>
    <string name="description_9">This is the Light House.</string>
    <string name="description_10">THis is the Stadhouderspoort.</string>
    <string name="description_12">This is the Grote Kerk.</string>
    <string name="description_13">This is the Bevrijdingsmonument.</string>
    <string name="description_11">At the Vishal you enter the Vismarktstraat; this street ends at the Havermarkt.  From the place where the fish market (1725) still indicates that there was a lively trade in sea fish here in the past, we walk through the Vismarktstraat to the Havermarkt. This market has been the entertainment center of Breda from the 1960s to the present day. Despite the name Havermarkt, it must be stated that the cereals are not here; but were traded on the Grote Markt. However, vegetables, eggs and butter were supplied and sold by farmers from the area. A leather market was also held here in the seventeenth century. The old names of this square were Groenmarkt, Botermarkt and Korenmarkt, which indicates the earlier functions a little better.  This was laid out around 1490 as a widening of the Visserstraat. If you grab a beer on a terrace on this delightful square in the summer, you will soon discover (even without that beer) that this square offers the best view of the large tower of the Grote Kerk. From this place you can also admire the beautiful broad substructure of that tower. There is much to see on this square. To the left on the corner of Havermarkt and Reigerstraat you will see the house \\\'De Arent\\\', built around 1490. It now has a seventeenth-century stepped gable and was completely restored in 1966 and converted into a restaurant. Opposite you on the Havermarkt are two more buildings that deserve your attention. Havermarkt number 5 dates from the sixteenth and seventeenth centuries. \\\'De Vogelstruys\\\' on Havermarkt 21 is a remarkable seventeenth-century monument with a high, non-symmetrical stepped gable. This house has also had many functions and destinations over the centuries. It was, among other things, a refuge house for the sisters of Catharinadal in the seventeenth century. Four statuettes were made for the \\\'De Troubadour\\\' statue, which adorns the end of Havermarkt. The other three were unveiled in Diest, Orange and Dillenburg, the sister cities of Breda in the Union of Orange Cities, which was established in 1963. A little further in the Visserstraat (no. 31), on the right-hand side, is a beautiful brick house from the 17th century with the remains of a sixteenth-century gothic house, called the Three Moors.</string>
</resources>